Challenge to do 100 things with AI
Episode 61
Learned a new skill again
This kid is my little brother
And this is his story
Late at night, our little boy
already nestled in the warm little quilt
sweetly asleep
Suddenly, a soft, twinkling, magical beam of light
Whoosh, it fell down from the night sky outside the window.
But is this really just a dream?
Look, in his little hand
still holding a sparkling little crystal
is flickering and glowing
The story just now was naturally fake
But this picture book is real
This is a little New Year's gift I gave him this year.
If he likes it and wants more
I can whip up countless for him in no time
a physical picture book featuring him as the protagonist
that skill of mine to create picture books
This time it was given to me by Kouzi
And this physical picture book was created through the official event 'Shake Off the Button' on Kozi
New Year's gift is coming soon
The production process is very simple
Click the arrow in the bottom right corner of the Home in Kozi Space
pop up more menus
Select the Skill Store, install and use this New Year picture book skill
Then upload a photo
whether it's your family or friends
cats or dogs
even complete strangers can
Then enter very simple prompt words
Describe the requirements for this picture book
Tell me roughly what the story is about
you can directly click send
Just wait a moment
A new storybook is just created like this.
Look at this 20-page picture book
consistent style
consistent character
consistent format, along with fully automated stories
fully automated voice-over
Everything can be done at once
No complex workflows are needed, no complicated workflow connections are required, no complex workflows are necessary
no complex workflow connections are needed
nor does it require programming, let alone the hassle of traditional AI chat tools
even if you chat back and forth with the AI over and over again
still have to face the same task requirements
the frustration of getting varying results each time
In Kouzi
In Kouzi's case, it directly adds a fixed skill to the large AI model.
This skill is like an SOP
allows the AI to follow a fixed process and steps
more completely and carefully execute tasks for you
and only use it when you need it
just like the picture book skill I showed you earlier
No matter who uses this skill, the format and results of the output picture book
will be exactly the same as what I showed you
And such complete and powerful skills
There are many more in the Skill Store.
You see, there are ones specifically for writing novels
specializing in map-making
generate games
making Comics and so on
As for the physical picture book I mentioned earlier
Just log in to Kouzi now to claim your free points.
Invite friends to participate together and you can also earn points
Alright, that's all for this video.
If you like my video
Remember to like, follow, and favorite
I'm Bob
See you in the next episode